<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scrum Blog by Vishwas</title>
    <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Scrum Blog by Vishwas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 18:55:31 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Product_developer</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/product_developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 18:55:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/product_developer/</guid>
      <description>Development Team Development Team
The Development Team paperwork an necessary a part of a larger Scrum crew. It is created from specialists who supply a probably releasable Increment of “Done” product on the give up of each Sprint. At the Sprint Review, a “Done” increment is required. Typically, most effective the participants of the Development Team create this Increment.
Development Teams are dependent nicely and empowered via way of means of the employer to efficiently manipulate their personal paintings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product_owner</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/product_owner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 18:54:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/product_owner/</guid>
      <description>Product Owner Product Owner
Scrum is a framework designed to assist the crew with a view to increase complicated products, scrum determines 3 crucial roles- product proprietor, scrum grasp, and crew member.
The product proprietor is chargeable for the product this is to be evolved. Scrum grasp courses the crew in every and each method and makes positive that the method is completed primarily based totally at the Scrum framework. Development crew takes element in figuring out the way to supply what the product proprietor has requested for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum_responsiblity</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum_responsiblity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 18:53:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum_responsiblity/</guid>
      <description>Roles &amp;amp; Responsibilities of a Scrum Master - Deep Dive A Scrum Master (Scrum Master), popularly called the “servant chief” is a train, motivator and chief of an Agile group. The function of a Scrum Master is to teach the group on Agile tactics and assist group contributors comply with Scrum practices religiously.
A excellent Scrum Master allows to set up a excessive-acting group dynamic, a non-stop glide, and an exponential development in tactics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum_framework_only</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum_framework_only/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 18:35:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum_framework_only/</guid>
      <description>Scrum Framework Scrum isn&amp;rsquo;t always only a method which presents a sequence of sequences to help you to supply a wonderful product on time and inside a budget. Rather, Scrum is a method framework that permits addressing complicated issues to supply merchandise of the best feasible cost. At the start of 1990, while Scrum become in its infancy, groups began out the usage of the Scrum framework to construct the goods the usage of diverse strategies and techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum_planning</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum_planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 18:12:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum_planning/</guid>
      <description>Sprint Planning A listing of to-do obligations withinside the Sprint is deliberate for the duration of Sprint Planning. This making plans is carried out through the crew collaboratively.
What is the length of Sprint Planning assembly? Sprint Planning lasts for eight hours for a one-month Sprint. The length may be shorter for shorter Sprints. The Scrum Master is chargeable for the occasion and makes certain that the crew participants recognize its purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum_retrospective</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum_retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 17:53:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum_retrospective/</guid>
      <description>Sprint Retrospective Sprint RestrospectiveRegardless of ways precise your Scrum group is, there may be constantly room for development. A precise Scrum group will constantly recognition on non-stop development possibilities just like the group must set a goal, and feature a scheduled length of the plan on the give up of the every Sprint. Therefore, it displays on how they may be going to locate the methods to enhance. This can be occurring at some stage in the “Sprint Retrospective”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprintreview</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/sprintreview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:04:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/sprintreview/</guid>
      <description>Sprint Review Sprint evaluate is an casual assembly held on the give up of the Sprint in which the increment is provided to sell the collaboration and achieve the customer’s comments at the evolved product. It is particularly performed to ‘Inspect’ the Increment and ‘Adapt’ the Product Backlog if required.
What is the reason of the Sprint Review? While growing a product in Scrum, it&amp;rsquo;s miles obligatory to supply a doubtlessly shippable product increment on the give up of each Sprint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dailyscrum</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/dailyscrum/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:04:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/dailyscrum/</guid>
      <description>How do you start your day at paintings? In Scrum, the group holds a &amp;lsquo;Daily Scrum&amp;rsquo; assembly for every and each day of a dash. The Daily Scrum assembly is precisely held with a 15-minute time-boxed occasion for the Development group.
The Daily Scrum is likewise called the Daily Scrum Stand-up assembly due to the not unusualplace practices made for every body are normally accompanied through status all through the complete length of the assembly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volocitysprint</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/volocitysprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:03:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/volocitysprint/</guid>
      <description>What is Velocity-primarily based totally Sprint Planning? The maximum vital degree that an Agile group will use in making plans is its “Velocity”. It is the quantity of labor completed via way of means of the group in every dash. It facilitates the group to become aware of how a great deal development they are able to intention to make in a given dash. Velocity is calculated via way of means of including all of the tale factors given to every consumer tale this is finished via way of means of the quit of the dash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capacitysprint</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/capacitysprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:02:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/capacitysprint/</guid>
      <description>There are approaches of Sprint Planning.
Velocity-primarily based totally Sprint Planning Capacity-primarily based totally Sprint Planning Velocity-primarily based totally making plans of the Sprint determines how a whole lot paintings the crew can accomplish withinside the Sprint. In any Sprint, the rate is calculated because the wide variety of Story factors finished in line with dash. This is a primary creation to Velocity-primarily based totally Sprint making plans. We will study greater approximately this kind of dash making plans withinside the subsequent section .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whatissprint</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/whatissprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:01:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/whatissprint/</guid>
      <description>A Sprint is the coronary heart of Scrum with quick everyday iterations with not a larger time-field of 2-four weeks. The Scrum Sprint purpose is to hold quick iterations with sufficient time among one week to at least one month to preserve the Scrum crew targeted on capability transport of a product increment. Even aleven though exceptions are allowed below positive boundaries, however Sprints ought to be of steady length. According to the rule, no purpose ought to be altered in the scope of the Sprint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrumhisotry</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrumhisotry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 13:59:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrumhisotry/</guid>
      <description>Industries, each IT and Non-IT, have gone through a Scrum revolution withinside the current past. What began out as a manner of method simplification in a collaborative surroundings have become an industry-huge phenomenon. Today, Scrum is a family call withinside the in large part matured company ecosystem. The records of Scrum has loads to spread approximately the origin, evolution, and the revolutionary improvement of the framework.
1993: A 12 months of first Scrum Looking again at Scrum, it changed into first applied in 1993 via way of means of Jeff Sutherland, John Scumniotales, and Jeff McKenna on the Easel Corporation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum versus kanban</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:34:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum9/</guid>
      <description>Because scrum and kanban each fall beneathneath the agile framework umbrella, many humans confuse them or suppose they may be the identical thing. There are differences, however. For one, scrum is extra precise to software program improvement groups, at the same time as kanban is utilized by many forms of groups and makes a speciality of presenting a visible illustration of an agile group&amp;rsquo;s workflow. Some argue that kanban is ready getting matters done, and scrum is ready speakme approximately getting matters done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile versus waterfall</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:32:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum8/</guid>
      <description>Both were round for a few time, with Waterfall acting a few 50 years in the past and Agile, a relative newcomer, at approximately twenty years old. Both emerged as equipment for basically coping with software program improvement however are actually broadly carried out throughout very exceptional styles of tasks.
WHAT IS THE DIFFERENCE? To placed it in reality Waterfall is basically making a terrific plan and sticking to it, even as Agile utilises a extra flexible, iterative technique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum7</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:29:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum7/</guid>
      <description>The tempo of virtual disruption is placing even massive groups vulnerable to closure. Startups are the usage of disruption to their gain via way of means of embracing strong methods and growing precise commercial enterprise models. This excessive opposition and disruption warrants agencies to maintain evolving so as to thrive. They can try this via way of means of growing modern-day structures and software program, adopting pragmatic methodologies, and embracing an organizational tradition that motivates innovation, agility and teamwork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum6</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:19:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum6/</guid>
      <description>What is SAFe SAFe or Scaled Agile Framework is a set of principles, processes, and best practices that assists organizations in adopting agile values and principles to build products or solutions at an enterprise level. It is one of several Agile frameworks designed to guide enterprises in scaling Agile practices beyond individual teams to deal with alignment and collaboration challenges. SAFe leverages three primary bodies of knowledge: Agile Software Development, Lean Product Development, and System Thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum5</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:18:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum5/</guid>
      <description>Purpose The motive purpose of this text is to discover the Pros and Cons (or Advantages and Dis-advantages) of SAFe as I see them. It isn&amp;rsquo;t always meant to examine SAFe with different frameworks however connection with Agile Manifesto and Principles can be made. Pros 2.1 Combines one of a kind Agile idea approaches in a single place Dean Leffingwell as someone and SAFe as a Framework have installed a whole lot of attempt to mix numerous Lean and Agile idea approaches and attempted to amalgamate the quality thoughts into one place — the SAFe Framework — viz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum4</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:16:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum4/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve in no way heard of it earlier than, the Scaled Agile Framework for Enterprise is a group of ideas and practices assembled with the aim of providing a manner to “scale up” an Agile operating version for massive organizations. If you want it, I actually have a refresher on what Agile is and isn’t right here. Since its inception in 2011, SAFe has skilled full-size growth. Almost 1/2 of one million humans international have emerge as licensed SAFe practitioners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum3</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 23:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum3/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Scrum is one of the agile methodologies designed to manual groups withinside the iterative and incremental transport of a product. Often called “an agile assignment control framework,” its consciousness is on the usage of an empirical technique that lets in groups to reply rapidly, efficiently, and successfully to extrade. Traditional assignment control strategies restore necessities with the intention to manipulate time and value; Scrum on the opposite hand, fixes time and value with the intention to manipulate necessities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum2</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 23:38:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum2/</guid>
      <description>A Better Way Of Building Products Scrum Guide CoverScrum is a framework inside which humans can cope with complicated adaptive problems, at the same time as productively and creatively handing over merchandise of the best feasible cost.
Scrum is a light-weight framework that facilitates humans, groups and companies generate cost via adaptive answers for complicated problems. Scrum co-creators Ken Schwaber and Jeff Sutherland have written The Scrum Guide to give an explanation for Scrum genuinely and succinctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum1</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 23:28:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Modern utility improvement is hardly ever a solitary attempt. Designing, coding, testing, and packaging packages calls for a cross-practical crew related to designers, developers, testers and picture artists running collaboratively and every proudly owning obligations depending on different individuals of the crew. This is made extra tough through the reality that necessities are extra regularly than now no longer unknown or incomplete. Combined those make the technique of growing packages that meet person expectancies, are stable, and are brought inside time and finances constraints a particularly complicated enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
