<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scrum Blog by Vishwas</title>
    <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Scrum Blog by Vishwas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:34:08 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Scrum versus kanban</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:34:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum9/</guid>
      <description>Because scrum and kanban each fall beneathneath the agile framework umbrella, many humans confuse them or suppose they may be the identical thing. There are differences, however. For one, scrum is extra precise to software program improvement groups, at the same time as kanban is utilized by many forms of groups and makes a speciality of presenting a visible illustration of an agile group&amp;rsquo;s workflow. Some argue that kanban is ready getting matters done, and scrum is ready speakme approximately getting matters done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile versus waterfall</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:32:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum8/</guid>
      <description>Both were round for a few time, with Waterfall acting a few 50 years in the past and Agile, a relative newcomer, at approximately twenty years old. Both emerged as equipment for basically coping with software program improvement however are actually broadly carried out throughout very exceptional styles of tasks.
WHAT IS THE DIFFERENCE? To placed it in reality Waterfall is basically making a terrific plan and sticking to it, even as Agile utilises a extra flexible, iterative technique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum7</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:29:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum7/</guid>
      <description>The tempo of virtual disruption is placing even massive groups vulnerable to closure. Startups are the usage of disruption to their gain via way of means of embracing strong methods and growing precise commercial enterprise models. This excessive opposition and disruption warrants agencies to maintain evolving so as to thrive. They can try this via way of means of growing modern-day structures and software program, adopting pragmatic methodologies, and embracing an organizational tradition that motivates innovation, agility and teamwork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum6</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:19:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum6/</guid>
      <description>What is SAFe SAFe or Scaled Agile Framework is a set of principles, processes, and best practices that assists organizations in adopting agile values and principles to build products or solutions at an enterprise level. It is one of several Agile frameworks designed to guide enterprises in scaling Agile practices beyond individual teams to deal with alignment and collaboration challenges. SAFe leverages three primary bodies of knowledge: Agile Software Development, Lean Product Development, and System Thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum5</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:18:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum5/</guid>
      <description>Purpose The motive purpose of this text is to discover the Pros and Cons (or Advantages and Dis-advantages) of SAFe as I see them. It isn&amp;rsquo;t always meant to examine SAFe with different frameworks however connection with Agile Manifesto and Principles can be made. Pros 2.1 Combines one of a kind Agile idea approaches in a single place Dean Leffingwell as someone and SAFe as a Framework have installed a whole lot of attempt to mix numerous Lean and Agile idea approaches and attempted to amalgamate the quality thoughts into one place — the SAFe Framework — viz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum4</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:16:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum4/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve in no way heard of it earlier than, the Scaled Agile Framework for Enterprise is a group of ideas and practices assembled with the aim of providing a manner to “scale up” an Agile operating version for massive organizations. If you want it, I actually have a refresher on what Agile is and isn’t right here. Since its inception in 2011, SAFe has skilled full-size growth. Almost 1/2 of one million humans international have emerge as licensed SAFe practitioners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum3</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 23:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum3/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Scrum is one of the agile methodologies designed to manual groups withinside the iterative and incremental transport of a product. Often called “an agile assignment control framework,” its consciousness is on the usage of an empirical technique that lets in groups to reply rapidly, efficiently, and successfully to extrade. Traditional assignment control strategies restore necessities with the intention to manipulate time and value; Scrum on the opposite hand, fixes time and value with the intention to manipulate necessities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum2</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 23:38:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum2/</guid>
      <description>A Better Way Of Building Products Scrum Guide CoverScrum is a framework inside which humans can cope with complicated adaptive problems, at the same time as productively and creatively handing over merchandise of the best feasible cost.
Scrum is a light-weight framework that facilitates humans, groups and companies generate cost via adaptive answers for complicated problems. Scrum co-creators Ken Schwaber and Jeff Sutherland have written The Scrum Guide to give an explanation for Scrum genuinely and succinctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum1</title>
      <link>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 23:28:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwas1234567.github.io/scrumblogbyvishwas/posts/scrum1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Modern utility improvement is hardly ever a solitary attempt. Designing, coding, testing, and packaging packages calls for a cross-practical crew related to designers, developers, testers and picture artists running collaboratively and every proudly owning obligations depending on different individuals of the crew. This is made extra tough through the reality that necessities are extra regularly than now no longer unknown or incomplete. Combined those make the technique of growing packages that meet person expectancies, are stable, and are brought inside time and finances constraints a particularly complicated enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
